PRAY WITH T.B. JOSHUA - BE RESCUED!!!
I want to pray for you.
Stretch your hand right now, in the name of Jesus.
Whatever chain satan might have used to connect you to himself, be disconnected!
Whatever chain satan might have used to connect you to himself, say, "I am disconnected!"
Say, "be disconnected!"
Be disconnected!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ! Amen!
Jesus loves you.
Tell yourself, "Jesus loves me."
He is concerned about you.
I said, God is concerned about you.
He is concerned about my spiritual life.
He is concerned about my finances.
He is concerned about my business.
He is concerned about my career.
He is concerned about my marital life.
You know that whatever satan might have used to connect you to himself:
chain of poverty, chain of setback, chain of limitation.
I say be broken! Be broken!
In the name of Jesus!
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
Be rescued, in the name of Jesus!
Be rescued!
Your finances, be rescued!
Your business, be rescued!
Your career, be rescued!
Say, "Be rescued!"
Say, "I rescue you, in the name of Jesus!"
Manifestation of Evil Spirits.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
You know to be rescued.
When you are rescued, your life is rescued.
I mean, everything about you is rescued.
You are rescued, in the name of Jesus!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
You satan, you demon, I call you by name, leave them alone!
Leave my people alone, in the name of Jesus!
I disconnect you from whatever chain satan might have used to connect you.
I disconnect you from satan!
I disconnect you from demons!
I disconnect you! Be disconnected!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
I can see you being delivered!
This is a prophetic word - I can see you being delivered.
This is a prophetic word - I can see your business being delivered.
This is a prophetic word - I prophesy to you, your business is free!
I prophesy to your life, your career is free!
I prophesy to your life, the way out for you has come!
Confess it, "The way out for me has come!"
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Viewers at home, where can you go from His presence?
Listen to me, the way out for you has come!
I said, the way out for your business has come.
Those of you on the sickbed, I say to you, "Dry bones shall rise again!"
Let there be light!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Those of us on the sickbed -
You have been on the sickbed for many years; you have been sick.
I say renew your strength!
Begin to renew your strength, in the name of Jesus!
Renew your bones, in the name of Jesus!
Renew your fluids, in the name of Jesus!
Renew your strength, in the name of Jesus!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
I say to you, check yourself, move around, move your limbs, move your system,
because the way out for your health has come.
The owner of the soul, the owner of the bones has replaced it.
The owner of the fluids has replaced it.
The owner of the bones has replaced it.
The owner of your body has touched it.
Jesus is the owner; He has touched you.
Be touched, be healed, be delivered, in the name of Jesus!
He is the owner of your business and your finances.
He is concerned about your finances, business, marital life and career.
Right now, in the name of Jesus, be free!
He wants you to be free. Be free!
He wants your business to be free. Be free!
He wants your career to be free. Be free!
He wants your finances to be free. Be free!
Say, "I am free!"
Hear the voice of God.
Breakthrough!
Breakthrough in my business!
Breakthrough in my career!
Breakthrough in my finances!
Breakthrough in my marital life!
Breakthrough in my career!
Breakthrough!
Do you know the meaning of breakthrough?
Where there is no way, God provides a way for you.
As from today, where there is no way, Jesus will provide a way.
All things are possible.
All things will begin to be possible for you, in the name of Jesus!
Who says he wants evidence?
Answer to your prayer is evidence.
Receive this answer.
The answer has been provided, in Jesus name!
Begin to share your testimony!
I am justified; I am no longer condemned.
Defeat and failures are things of the past.
I am born again!
I am healed!
I am delivered!
Thank you, Jesus!
"Thank you, Jesus!" is my testimony.
Thank you, Jesus, for my finances.
Thank you, Jesus, for my business.
Thank you, Jesus, for my marital life.
Thank you, Jesus, for my career.
Thank you!
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here, to subscribe, to witness more of God's power and work in our generation today,
and to stay up-to-date with our latest prophesies, deliverances, sermons, and testimonies
from the Synagogue Church of All Nations.
Emmanuel TV. Changing lives, changing nations, and changing the world.